<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Hal Quotes</string>
    <string name="edit_message">Enter a message</string>
    <string name="button_send">Generate Hal Quote</string>
    <string name="clear">New Quote</string>
    <string name="restart">Back To Main Screen</string>
    <string-array name="quotes_array">
        <item>\"If you want me to wear a singlet, you need to look for a bigger one. Im not going to wear one thats going to put me in pain.\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"I just worked out and ordered a bacon ultimate cheeseburger.\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"I think I\'ve watched the playboy channel for 20 hours in the last 3 days.\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"My package is going to be ripping out of that singlet. Im going to twist my balls around so it confuses whoever looks at it.\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"so apparently I started playing leanne. in words with friends and I dont remember. I blacked out that morning we had brunch\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"I just yelled TESTES!!! in the office\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"taco bell.so good\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"Zeezee ate my fucking hat\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"this time you make it out to the bars. and this time I keep my dick in my pants\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"I requested the first weekend of March off so that might mean I have an irregular schedule\" - Hal \n\n \"youre an irregular guy\" -me \n\n \"with an irregular taste for women\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"I got my fat bitches out of the way\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"One does not go from stealing old ladies purses to being a civil drunk\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"I need to stop doing stupid shit like hitting on nasty chicks\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"if were checking bags in we have to do it 45 minutes before the flight fyi\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"Theres a REALLY hot asian girl applying to be a geologist and my boss won\'t hire her just to troll me\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"I should have made her eat dog food\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"I fucked a big yum yum last night. im still kinda drunk\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"I got paid. Fed my fat friend magnolia and started driving. And snorted coke off my penis\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"My office is right by the bathroom. Everyone has taken a dump today it sucks\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"My coworkers said I just spoke jibberish whenever someone talked to me\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"The moment I see toilet water rising my heart starts racing.\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"I shouted WORST SEX EVER. she didnt like that\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"lol I saw that monkey riding the dog live. I spit out my food yelling for my coworker to look\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"Taco bell literally saved my life\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"I just nailed a cardinal with my car. I\'ve been smiling way too long\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"I was having a fake interview. and was asked, whats your greatest weakness. I said asian girls\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"duuuuude. the McRib is out. Im going to get 4 of them tonight. and watch the rangers dominate\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"Fucking andre johnson. Fucking Mario Williams. Fucking tit sandwich. Titties\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"I took a dump in the office to find out the water is no longer working. my shit will marinate for a day or two in there\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"I left my number for a hot asian waitress yesterday\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"did I tell you about the porta potty incident? I opened one up and saw an old lady peeing\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"is that like braveheart. except I go around pooping in cars with war paint\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"we\'re all born dirty. Im just one with nature\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"French woman do have massive bushes. While on acid last night I got one naked, said "bonswa" and ran out of her apartment\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"you think girls like banana dicks?\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"oh man, I had an epicly close shart moment. I walked into somenone elses office tried to fart and had to waddle to the bathroom\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"Let\'s get Mikey a finger monkey for Christmas\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"I keep telling Ryan I\'m going to poop on his dick\" - Hal Peters</item>
        <item>\"You know what\'s the best thing about younger guys?\" - Hal \n\n \"What?\" - Older Lady \n\n \"Stamina.\" - Hal \n\n \"You\'ve told me that three times already.\" - Older Lady</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
